<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zera</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hola fragmento en blanco</string>
    <string name="language">Idioma</string>

    <string name="number_zero">0</string>
    <string name="number_one">1</string>
    <string name="number_two">2</string>
    <string name="number_three">3</string>
    <string name="number_four">4</string>
    <string name="number_five">5</string>
    <string name="number_six">6</string>
    <string name="number_seven">7</string>
    <string name="number_eight">8</string>
    <string name="number_nine">9</string>
    <string name="btn_clear">Claro</string>
    <string name="btn_backspace">atrás</string>

    <string name="logout">¿Estás seguro de cerrar sesión en esta aplicación?</string>
    <string name="exit_screen">Seguro que si quieres salir de esta aplicación</string>
    <string name="no_internet">Sin conexión a Internet \n Vaya a configuración y conéctese a la red.</string>
    <string name="error_msg">Vuelve a intentarlo, algo salió mal</string>
    <string name="dialog_permission_title">Conceder permisos</string>
    <string name="dialog_permission_message">Esta aplicación necesita permiso para usar esta función. Puedes otorgarlos en la configuración de la aplicación.</string>
    <string name="go_to_settings">IR A LA CONFIGURACIÓN</string>

    <string name="language_english">en</string>
    <string name="language_hindi">ar</string>




    <string name="validation_name">Por favor ingrese el nombre.</string>
    <string name="validation_firstname">Por favor ingrese su nombre.</string>
    <string name="validation_lastname">Por favor ingrese su apellido.</string>
    <string name="validation_mobile_length">Introduzca un número de móvil válido</string>
    <string name="validation_email">Por favor introduzca un correo electrónico válido.</string>
    <string name="validation_password">Por favor, ingrese contraseña.</string>
    <string name="validation_valid_password">La contraseña debe tener un mínimo de seis caracteres.</string>
    <string name="validation_termsCondtions">Acepta los términos y condiciones.</string>

    <string name="validation_city">Por favor ingrese la ciudad.</string>
    <string name="validation_dateOfBirth">Seleccione la fecha de nacimiento.</string>
    <string name="validation_state">Ingrese el estado.</string>
    <string name="validation_oldpassword">Introduzca la contraseña anterior.</string>
    <string name="validation_newpassword">Por favor ingrese nueva contraseña.</string>
    <string name="validation_cpassword">Por favor ingrese confirmar contraseña.</string>

    <string name="validation_valid_cpassword">La nueva contraseña y la contraseña de confirmación deben ser las mismas.</string>
    <string name="validation_mobile">Introduzca el número de móvil.</string>

    <string name="validation_money">Ingrese una cantidad válida</string>
    <string name="validation_termPeriod">Seleccione el período de término</string>
    <string name="validation_valid_mobile">Ingrese un número de teléfono válido.</string>
    <string name="validation_comment">Por favor ingrese un comentario</string>
    <string name="validation_address">Por favor ingrese la direccion</string>
    <string name="delivery_address">Dirección de entrega</string>
    <string name="validation_money_withdraw">El monto del retiro excede el monto disponible</string>
    <string name="validation_money_redeposit">La cantidad de depósito excede la cantidad disponible</string>
    <string name="validation_zero_amount">El monto del retiro no puede ser cero</string>
    <string name="minimumAmount500">El monto del retiro no puede ser cero</string>
    <string name="validation_zeroDeposit_amount">El monto del depósito no puede ser cero</string>
    <string name="changePassword">Cambiar la contraseña</string>
    <string name="currentPassword">Contraseña actual</string>
    <string name="newPassword">Nueva contraseña</string>
    <string name="confirmPassword">confirmar Contraseña</string>
    <string name="save">Ahorrar</string>
    <string name="passwordSuccess">Contraseña cambiada con éxito</string>
    <string name="renewAccount">Renovar cuenta</string>
    <string name="deleteUser">Eliminar confirmación</string>
    <string name="confirmations">Confirmación</string>
    <string name="userDeleteConfirmation">¿Realmente quieres eliminar a este usuario?</string>
    <string name="addSignHeader">Por favor firme abajo</string>


    <!--    pdfs-->
    <string name="pdfTitle">ZERA</string>
    <string name="companyRepresentative">Luis A. Romero, Representative, Zera Financial</string>
    <string name="maturityDate">Maturity Date -</string>
    <string name="termLength">Term Length -</string>
    <string name="interestRate">Interest Rate -</string>
    <string name="date">Date -</string>
    <string name="minimumTerm">MINIMUM TERM</string>
    <string name="sixmonth">6 Months</string>
    <string name="oneYear">1 Year</string>
    <string name="twoyear">2 Years</string>
    <string name="depositAmount">DEPOSIT AMOUNTS</string>
    <string name="amt500">$500-$15,000</string>
    <string name="StartingAmount">Starting Amount -</string>
    <string name="amt15000">$15,001-$100,000</string>
    <string name="amount1L">$100,001+</string>
    <string name="monthlyInterestRate">MONTHLY INTEREST RATE</string>
    <string name="rate5">5%/Month</string>
    <string name="currentInterest">Current Interest Rates For Any New Accounts</string>
    <string name="renewalPolicy"><b>RENEWAL POLICY –</b> The account will automatically renew at maturity unless you notify us
within the 3-day grace period after the maturity date that you do not want the account to
automatically renew. If you choose to let the account automatically renew, the term will renew as
the same term as before. If you do not notify us, the renewal term will be the same as the
original term, beginning on the maturity date (unless we notify you, in writing, before a maturity
date, of a different term for renewal).</string>
    <string name="interest"><b>INTEREST –</b> The interest rate on your account is a fixed rate. The initial interest rate is stated in
the welcome letter sent to you at the e-mail address you provided at the account opening. </string>
    <string name="maturity_Date"><b>MATURITY DATE –</b>  Confirmation of your maturity date, based on the term you selected at
account opening and the date we receive the deposit to fund the account, will be sent to you in
a welcome letter at the e-mail address you provided us when you opened the account.</string>
    <string name="rateInfo"><b>RATE INFORMATION – </b> We guarantee the disclosed interest rate for 3 days from the date of
the account opening. You must fund the account within this time period. If you do not fund the
account within 3 days of account opening, the interest rate will be the prevailing interest rate at
the time we receive the deposit. In any case, the account must be funded within 3 days of
opening or it will be closed. \n\nConfirmation of your interest rate will be sent to you in a welcome letter at the e-mail address
you provided us when you opened the account. The interest rate will be paid out monthly and or
reinvested in the account. Interest begins to accrue on the business day we receive your
deposit of any non-cash item (for example, a check) to fund the account.
\n\nInterest will be compounded and credited monthly/annually, unless you have selected otherwise
in which case interest will be compounded and credited at maturity. If you choose, you may
have interest paid to you each month or reinvested into account.
\n\nThe interest rate stated in your welcome letter assumes that interest remains on deposit until
maturity. A withdrawal of interest will reduce earnings.</string>
    <string name="minimumBalance"><b>MINIMUM BALANCE REQUIREMENT –</b>  You must make a minimum deposit of $500 to open
the account. You must maintain this minimum balance on a daily basis to earn the interest rate
disclosed.</string>
    <string name="noOfEndorsment"><b>NUMBER OF ENDORSEMENTS –</b>  Only one endorsement by any named owner is required to
withdraw or renegotiate the terms of the account. </string>
    <string name="withdrawPenality"><b>WITHDRAWALS OF INTEREST –</b> Withdrawals of accrued interest during a term are permitted
without penalty.</string>
    <string name="earlyWithdrawal"><b>EARLY WITHDRAWAL PENALTY- </b>If we consent to a request for a withdrawal that is
otherwise not permitted, you may have to pay a penalty. The penalty amount will be determined
as follows:
\n\n15% penalty of total account funds </string>
    <string name="transctionalLimit"><b>TRANSACTION LIMITATIONS</b> – You may make additional deposits to the accounts principal
during a term (if deposit is after withdrawal date and or after 72 grace period, interest will not
start occurring until next withdrawal date). You cannot withdraw principal from the account
without our consent except on or after maturity. (For accounts that automatically renew, there is
a grace period after each renewal date during which withdrawals are permitted without penalty.)
In certain circumstances, such as the death or incompetence of an account owner, the law
permits, and in some cases requires, the waiver of the early withdrawal penalty. Other
exceptions may also apply, for example, if this is part of an IRA or other tax-deferred savings
plan.
\n\nInterest earned during one term that is not withdrawn during or immediately after the term is
added to principal for the renewal term. The rate for each renewal term will be determined by us
on or just before the renewal date. You may call us on or shortly before the maturity date and we
can tell you what the interest rate will be for the next renewal term.</string>
    <string name="balancecompution"><b>BALANCE COMPUTATION METHOD –</b> We use the daily balance method to calculate the
interest on this account. This method applies a daily periodic rate to the principal in the account
each day.</string>
    <string name="setOff"><b>SETOFF –</b> You each agree that we may (when permitted by law) set off funds in this account
against any due and payable debt owed to us now or in the future, by any of you having the
right of withdrawal, to the extent of such person’s or legal entity’s right to withdraw. If the debt
arises from a note, “any due and payable debt” includes the total amount of which we are
entitled to demand payment under the terms of the note at the time we set off, including any
balance for which we properly accelerate under the note. This right to set-off does not apply to
the account if: (a) it is an Individual Retirement Account or other tax-deferred retirement
account, or (b) the debt is created by a consumer credit transaction under a credit card</string>
    <string name="withdrawTransfers"><b>WITHDRAWALS AND TRANSFERS –</b> Only those of you who sign the permanent signature
card may withdraw funds from the account. (In appropriate cases, a court appointed
representative, a beneficiary of a trust or pay-on-death account whose right of withdrawal has
matured, or a newly appointed and authorized representative of a legal entity may also withdraw
from this account.) The specific number of you who must agree to any withdrawal is noted in the
section bearing the title Number of Endorsements. This means, for example, that if two of you
sign the signature card but only one endorsement is necessary for withdrawal then either of you
may request withdrawal of the entire account at any time. Unless otherwise specified in writing
only one endorsement is required to withdraw funds from this account. When withdrawing allow
5-7 business days for funds to be deposited.</string>
    <string name="primaryAgreement"><b>PRIMARY AGREEMENT –</b> You agree to keep your funds with us in the account until the
maturity date. (An automatically renewable account matures at regular intervals.) You may not
transfer this account without first obtaining our written consent. You must present this certificate
when you request a withdrawal or a transfer.
\n\nThe account is void if the deposit is made by a method requiring collection (such as a check)
and the deposit is not immediately collected in full. If the deposit is made or payable in a foreign
currency, the amount of the deposit will be adjusted to reflect final exchange into U.S. dollars.
\n\nRules governing changes in interest rates have been provided. For other changes, we will give
you reasonable notice of changes in writing or by any other method permitted by law.
\n\nIf any notice is necessary, you all agree that the notices will be sufficient if we mail it to the
address you have provided us. You must notify us of any change.</string>
    <string name="transfer"><b>TRANSFER –</b> “Transfer” means any change in ownership, withdrawal rights, or survivorship
rights, including (but not limited to) any pledge or assignment of this account as collateral. You
cannot transfer the account without our written consent.</string>
    <string name="definition"><b>DEFINITIONS –</b>
    “We,” “our,” and “us” mean the issuer of this account and “you” and “your”
    mean the depositor(s). “Account” means the original loan to us as well as the deposit it
    evidences.
</string>
    <string name="openingPolicy">This Agreement, along with any other documents we provide you pertaining to your loan to us
account, is a contract that establishes rules which control your account with us. Please read this
carefully. By agreeing with these terms and conditions and opening the account, you agree to
be bound by these rules.̥</string>


    <string name="styled_welcome_message">We are <b><i>so</i></b> glad to see you.</string>

    <string name="addBankOrCard">Agregar tarjeta o banco</string>
    <string name="accountNumber">Número de cuenta</string>
    <string name="routingNumber">Número de ruta</string>
    <string name="add">Agregar</string>
    <string name="addCard">Agregar tarjeta</string>
    <string name="nameOnCard">Nombre en la tarjeta</string>
    <string name="cardNumber">Número de tarjeta</string>
    <string name="expirationDate">Fecha de caducidad</string>
    <string name="addFunds">AÑADIR FONDOS</string>
    <string name="chooseAmount">Elegir la cantidad</string>
    <string name="swipeToDeposit">DESLIZA PARA DEPÓSITO</string>
    <string name="addAuthUser">Agregar usuario autorizado</string>
    <string name="email">Correo electrónico</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber">Número de teléfono</string>
    <string name="address">Dirección</string>
    <string name="state">Estado</string>
    <string name="city">ciudad</string>
    <string name="authUser">Usuarios autorizados</string>
    <string name="addUser">Agregar usuario</string>
    <string name="oldpassword">Contraseña anterior</string>
    <string name="hello">Hola</string>
    <string name="deposit_amount">Cantidad del depósito</string>
    <string name="termPeriod">Período de vigencia</string>
    <string name="years">Años</string>
    <string name="months">Meses</string>
    <string name="month">mes</string>
    <string name="summary">Resumen</string>
    <string name="principalBalance">saldo principal</string>
    <string name="fixedInterestRate">Tasa de interés fija</string>
    <string name="next">Próximo</string>
    <string name="howDoesitwork">¿Como funciona?</string>
    <string name="seeHowmuchIcanMake">¡Vea cuánto puedo ganar!</string>
    <string name="earningWithZera">Ganar con zera</string>
    <string name="principal">Principal</string>
    <string name="interestRates">Tasa de interés</string>
    <string name="totalEarned">Total ganado</string>
    <string name="payments">Pagos</string>
    <string name="totalWithdraw">Retiro total</string>
    <string name="allDone">Todo listo</string>
    <string name="fundAccount">Cuenta de fondos</string>
    <string name="userAddBankingInfoHere">El usuario agrega \n información bancaria \n aquí</string>
    <string name="generalInfo">Información general</string>
    <string name="userName">Nombre de usuario</string>
    <string name="howmuchIcanMake">¿Cuánto puedo ganar?</string>
    <string name="enterAmount">Ingrese la cantidad</string>
    <string name="principalDepositAmount">Monto del depósito principal</string>
    <string name="FivepercentPerMonth">5% cada mes</string>
    <string name="calculate">Calcular</string>
    <string name="welcomeBack">Bienvenido de nuevo!</string>
    <string name="signInToyourAccount">Iniciar sesión en su cuenta</string>
    <string name="yourEmail">Tu correo electrónico</string>
    <string name="password">Contraseña</string>
    <string name="forgotpassword">¿Has olvidado tu contraseña?</string>
    <string name="login">ACCESO</string>
    <string name="dontHaveAnAccount">¿No tienes una cuenta?</string>
    <string name="signUp">Inscribirse</string>
    <string name="emailLinkMessage">Recibirá un correo electrónico con un enlace para actualizar \n su contraseña.</string>
    <string name="resetpassword">Restablecer la contraseña</string>
    <string name="redeposit">REDEPOSITAR</string>
    <string name="availableToRedeposit">Disponible para volver a depositar</string>
    <string name="swipeToRedeposit">DESLIZA PARA REDEPOSITAR</string>
    <string name="letsStartWithBasics">Empecemos con lo básico</string>
    <string name="firstName">Primer nombre</string>
    <string name="lastname">Apellido</string>
    <string name="haveAnAccount">¿Ya tienes una cuenta?</string>
    <string name="edituser">editar usuario</string>
    <string name="delete_user">Borrar usuario</string>
    <string name="withdraw">RETIRAR</string>
    <string name="availableToWithDraw">Disponible para retirar</string>
    <string name="swipeToWithDraw">DESLIZAR PARA RETIRAR</string>
    <string name="yes">sí</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancelar</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="note">Nota</string>
    <string name="typeYourDescription">Escriba su descripción</string>
    <string name="okay">Okey</string>
    <string name="currentBalance">Saldo actual</string>
    <string name="incomingPayment">PAGO RECIBIDO</string>
    <string name="transction">ACTAS</string>
    <string name="noTransactions">No hay transacción disponible</string>
    <string name="profile">Perfil</string>
    <string name="bank">Banco</string>
    <string name="signOut">desconectar</string>
    <string name="searchFor">Buscar</string>
    <string name="overview">Visión general</string>
    <string name="maturity_date">Fecha de vencimiento</string>
    <string name="app_nameComplete">Zera Financiero</string>
    <string name="slide1Message">¡Reciba un pago fijo del 5% cada mes sobre \n su depósito de capital!</string>
    <string name="easyDepositWithdraw">Depósito \ny retiro fácil</string>
    <string name="slide2Message">Tú tienes el control. ¡Retirar y \n depositar todo con un clic de botón \n recibir fondos del mismo modo para el día siguiente!</string>
    <string name="saveAndSecure">Seguro y protegido</string>
    <string name="slide3Message">Asegurado con cifrado de 256 bits, \n nivel de seguridad bancario y asegurado \n con la FDIC.</string>
    <string name="step1">Paso 1</string>
    <string name="depositfundinAccount">Depositar fondos en su cuenta.</string>
    <string name="step1Message">Con un mínimo de $ 500 y \n sin límite máximo, su depósito está \n asegurado con la FDIC.</string>
    <string name="step2">Paso 2</string>
    <string name="chooseATimePeriod">Elija un período de término.</string>
    <string name="step2Message">Cuanto más tiempo se depositen los fondos \n más podrás ganar. Ver calculadora.</string>
    <string name="step3">Paso 3</string>
    <string name="interestAddUp">El interés se suma.</string>
    <string name="step3Message">Reciba un interés fijo del 5% cada \nmes sobre su depósito de capital.</string>
    <string name="step4">Paso 4</string>
    <string name="withdrawReinvestEveryMonth">Retirar o \n reinvertir cada mes.</string>

    <string name="trans_interest">Interesar</string>
    <string name="trans_open_Account">Cuenta abierta</string>
    <string name="trans_Referral">Remisión</string>
    <string name="trans_Withdraw">Retirar</string>
    <string name="dateofBirth">Fecha de cumpleaños</string>
    <string name="noUserAvailabile">Ningún usuario disponible</string>

    <string name="interestPaid">Pago interesado</string>
    <string name="newBalance">Nuevo equilibrio</string>
    <string name="custom">Personalizado</string>
    <string name="done">Hecho</string>


    <string name="ihaveread">he leído </string>
    <string name="and">y </string>
    <string name="aswellasacknowledge">así como \n reconocer el recibo de </string>
    <string name="termsOfuse"><u><b>Condiciones de uso</b></u> </string>
    <string name="policy"><u><b>Política,</b></u> </string>
    <string name="privacyNotice"><u><b>Aviso de Privacidad</b></u> </string>


</resources>